<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../../schema/out/cbml.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?>
<?xml-model href="../../schema/out/cbml.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xmlns:cbml="http://www.cbml.org/ns/1.0">
   <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title xml:id="s1e3">It's Granny vs. Granny Clash</title>
         </titleStmt>
         <publicationStmt>
            <p>Dandadan</p>
         </publicationStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <p>Information about the source</p>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
   </teiHeader>
   <text xml:lang="eng">
      <body>
         <div type="event" xml:id="s1e3-event1">
            <stage type="location" where="tvStudio"/>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>Your age is 27?</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Shoma">
               <speaker>Shoma</speaker>
               <p>I'm 20.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> You have a wife and child?</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Shoma">
               <speaker>Shoma</speaker>
               <p>I live alone</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>You like curry?</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Shoma">
               <speaker>Shoma</speaker>
               <p>I like ramen.</p>
            </sp>
         </div>
         <div type="event" xml:id="s1e3-event2">
            <stage type="location" where="backstage"/>
            <caption source="sign">CAN PSYCHIC POWERS EXPOSE?</caption>
            <sp who="extra">
               <speaker>staff1</speaker>
               <p>Santa Dodoria sure is something.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="extra">
               <speaker>staff2</speaker>
               <p>So flamboyantly wrong.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="staff1">
               <speaker>staff1</speaker>
               <p>There's no way such a young idol could have a wife and a kid. </p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="extra">
               <speaker>staff1</speaker>
               <p>Even I can see that.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="extra">
               <speaker>staff2</speaker>
               <p> Is it okay to air that as-is?</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="extra">
               <speaker>staff1</speaker>
               <p>Should be okay.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="extra">
               <speaker>staff2</speaker>
               <p> Nobody would be so pissed off at a local program like this one. </p>
            </sp>
         </div>
         <div type="event" xml:id="s1e3-event3">
            <stage type="location" where="car"/>
            <caption source="sign">VACANT</caption>
            <caption source="sign">CARRYING PASSENGERS</caption>
            <sp who="extra">
               <speaker>driver</speaker>
               <p>You're Santa Dodoria, aren't you? I saw you on TV the other day. Do you really
                  have psychic powers?</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>Here's fine. Drop me off.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="extra">
               <speaker>driver</speaker>
               <p> Huh? It's not like I'm trying to insult you or anything. I just wanted you to
                  show me. </p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> If you don't wanna die, hurry on and scram.</p>
            </sp>
         </div>
         <div type="event" xml:id="s1e3-event4">
            <stage type="location" where="road"/>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>Come on now, I thought you brought over yet another scumbag. </p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> But this one isn't even human. Sheesh. My grandkid only brings problems in. </p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>My skin's gonna get dry from all the stress. Come on. Bring it on. </p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>That was close! You're super fast! But things happened just as I predicted.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>I thought you'd come around to my blind spot.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>You fell into the trap that I had set up beforehand.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>If you cross that line, you'll die. That's a barrier right there. When you drive a
                  warding nail inside this circle, the inside of the circle turns into a barrier.
               </p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>But if you drive it outside the circle, the area outside of the circle becomes the
                  barrier. The reason you couldn't touch me was because I was protected by a
                  barrier. </p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="turboGranny">
               <speaker>turboGranny</speaker>
               <p>I'll make sure to eat and k*ll you. Don't think you can keep me trapped
                  forever.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>I don't wanna trap you. I wanna k*ll you. Come on, stand your ground, will ya?
                  You're gonna cross that line! What's wrong? When you're in there, you can't make
                  use of your speed that you're so proud of. </p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="turboGranny">
               <speaker>turboGranny</speaker>
               <p>You scummy old hag!</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>Did an old hag just call another old hag a scummy old hag? That pisses me off.
               </p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="turboGranny">
               <speaker>turboGranny</speaker>
               <p> If you burn me, this guy that I cursed will die, too. </p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> I'll k*ll off all scumbags who deceive my grandkid. Even if they're human. Bye.
               </p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="turboGranny">
               <speaker>turboGranny</speaker>
               <p>Scummy old hag!</p>
            </sp>
         </div>
         <div type="event" xml:id="s1e3-event5">
            <stage type="location" where="ayaseHome"/>
            <sp who="momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>Okarun! Hey, you were home? </p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>Shut up. I'm watching The Idiot Shogun.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>Anyway, I have something to talk about with you. </p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> You went to a spiritual hotspot?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>I did. Not me, but a friend.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> Why?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="momo">
               <speaker> Momo</speaker>
               <p> "Why?" Because we were talking and that's how things ended up.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>The Idiot Shogun is Japan's national treasure.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>Hey, were you listening? Anyway, did you see a guy? He'll be in big trouble if I'm
                  not around!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>If you're talking about the evil spirit, I k*lled it.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p> An evil spirit? What kind? Did it have glasses on?</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>Come on, you don't even believe in ghosts. Besides, I'm a fake spirit medium.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p> How long are you gonna hold that grudge, you scummy old hag. Something really bad
                  might happen, so just answer me!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> Stop it. Don't believe in those stories. There are no evil spirits, and I'm a
                  fake.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="momo">
               <speaker> Momo</speaker>
               <p>Grandma. I'm sorry. I was wrong. So please tell me. What did you do to the evil
                  spirit?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>Head over to the main shrine.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>Scummy old hag! If something's wrong with Okarun, I'll never forgive you!</p>
            </sp>
         </div>
         <div type="event" xml:id="s1e3-event6">
            <stage type="location" where="road"/>
            <!-- this is momo thoughts -->
            <sp who="momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>I didn't want to miss my chance. He was just an occult freak who simply wanted
                  friends. It's my fault. Because I forced him to go to that place! I'm sorry,
                  Okarun! Okarun!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="ken">
               <speaker>Ken</speaker>
               <p>Miss Ayase! I'm so glad! I thought that I'd m*rder*d you or something. Huh? Wait.
                  Miss Ayase? Miss Ayase?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="momo">
               <speaker> Momo</speaker>
               <p>You're still alive and well, scumbag four-eyes! What? What's up with that?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="ken">
               <speaker>Ken</speaker>
               <p> Well, I'm sorry I'm still alive!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p> I'm so irritated.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>Since when have you started being friends with monsters?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="momo">
               <speaker> Momo</speaker>
               <p>You scared me!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>The curse won't kick in as long as he's in there. But one step outside, and he's
                  back to a monster.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>What was that about k*lling him off? You lied to me.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> You seemed pretty desperate. You into brats like that?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>No way! Turbo Granny took his you-know-what. And she told me that as long as she
                  has it, his curse won't be lifted. I'm responsible for what happened to him, so I
                  just want to do something about it.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> Oh, I see. So you do like him.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo </speaker>
               <p>I didn't say that! Anyway, I can use psychic powers now.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>What the hell are you talkin' about?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>I went to this place where UFOs show up. A lot of stuff happened there, and now I
                  can use powers.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko </speaker>
               <p> But UFOs don't exist.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p> I totally get that reaction. I was just like that until yesterday.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker> Momo </speaker>
               <p>Anyway, it's true that I can use psychic powers now. And if I'm not holding back
                  Okarun's curse with it, he goes wild.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> I'm sure psychic powers exist.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>I don't know what your criteria for believing stuff is.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>Anyway, Turbo Granny, huh? You sure got your hands on a troublesome one.</p>
            </sp>
            <!-- the 2 next lines from Seiko below is the flashback where she is telling turbo granny backstory -->

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> In the past, she used to be called the Hundred Kilo Granny. She's a modern yokai
                  monster that wreaked havoc all over the country. And I heard such an elusive
                  entity had been dwelling for some time in that tunnel.I went over there once to
                  check things out.</p>
            </sp>
            <cbml:caption source="sign"> KEEP OUT</cbml:caption>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> It was most strange. I couldn't even get near the tunnel because of just how
                  strong the spiritual power was. You know about location-bound spirits? They're
                  spirits that stay in particular locations that they have strong attachments to.
                  They're basically the strongest within their territories. No spirit medium would
                  go up against a location-bound spirit. There was a location-bound spirit inside
                  that tunnel. Do you know what that means? Turbo Granny and that location-bound
                  spirit had fused together.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>Don't try to fight against it. I don't want to lose my dear grandchild.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> You're not directly involved with it, either. So forget about him. You should
                  return to everyday life.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>I wonder what the Mr. Ken I love would do in times like this. When I can't decide,
                  that's what I think. I've never had regret by choosing this way. And if this was
                  Mr. Ken, I'm 100% positive he'd go in and help. So that's what I'm gonna do!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>Mr. Ken, you say? -You're totally in love with that kid!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>No, that's not what I mean! I wasn't talking about him!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>Hey, she's confessing your love to you. How do you feel?</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>I told you that's not what I mean! I'm talking about the actor!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> Looks like I got no choice if you're gonna go that far. Go play tag with Turbo
                  Granny. That thing has absolute confidence in its running. A few random taunts and
                  it's sure to take the challenge. Now this is where the problem starts. The
                  location-bound spirit's territory is all of Shono City.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>You have to lure Turbo Granny outside of the city without getting caught. If you
                  can drag it away from its territory, it will get weak and even you guys will be
                  able to defeat it.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker> Momo </speaker>
               <p>Oh no, look at these feeble legs. There's no way in hell I can play tag against
                  Turbo Granny. Instead of doing something like that, can't you make something like
                  those barriers and deal with it? Like putting one up at the tunnel.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> I can't do that. I can't help out to begin with.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>Huh? What's up with that?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>My barrier spells only borrow the powers of the gods that live on this land. Once
                  we leave Kamigoe City where we live, I can't use these powers.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>Oh, so we have our own territory, too.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>All lands have their own gods. The problem is whether you're playing a home or an
                  away game. In any case, this is the only way to defeat Turbo Granny. If you start
                  physically training now, you should be able to become fast enough to run away from
                  her.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo </speaker>
               <p>Are you seriously saying that? No matter how hard I tried, I couldn't even make it
                  to the prefecture finals for track meets!</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> I'm not talking about you.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo </speaker>
               <p>Huh?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>I'm talking about him.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p> Oh, I see!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken </speaker>
               <p>You're finally including me into the conversation?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>Sorry, I forgot.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p> But Okarun, you have no stamina.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken</speaker>
               <p> None at all.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>And I have to keep control over your curse.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>Then he needs to run piggy-backing Momo.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken</speaker>
               <p> Miss Ayase, how much do you weigh?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>Hey, do ya wanna die?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker> Ken</speaker>
               <p>Oh no, it's just impossible! My limit for going full strength in cursed mode is
                  about twice!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p> Right!</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> Then train so that you can always be at full strength. Get to it. Push-ups,
                  sit-ups, back extensions, and squats. Five sets, 100 reps each.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken </speaker>
               <p>Huh?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>Do it. And Momo, same goes for your psychic powers. You need to power them up more
                  than what they are now. As I can't be of any help, you guys simply have to get
                  stronger. So I will be training the two of you. Go to sleep for today. We'll start
                  tomorrow. Four-eyes, start your physical training right now.</p>
            </sp>


            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken</speaker>
               <p> Oh, okay. Your granny is so young.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>Isn't she annoying?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken </speaker>
               <p>Miss Ayase, I'm so sorry.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo </speaker>
               <p>When I fought that big thing, I was honestly too desperate to think of anyone
                  other than myself. I'm really sorry.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>Oh, there's nothing you could've done about that.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken </speaker>
               <p> But Miss Ayase, you were different. You saved me and defeated the monster. But if
                  something like that happens again, I'll do my best so that I can save you. So
                  please don't be disappointed with me. Please, don't stop being a friend.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p> I wouldn't be disappointed. You're overthinking.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken</speaker>
               <p> Then why did you slam the door earlier?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>W-Well, that was…</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken</speaker>
               <p>See, there you go! You really were disappointed!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>I said I wasn't! But like, I am right now! You're such a pain!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken</speaker>
               <p> I'm sorry.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>You were pretty awesome when you were fighting. But you're kinda dense, Okarun.
                  I'll probably be saving you next time, too! You sleep there for today. I'll bring
                  you a futon right now.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken </speaker>
               <p>Miss Ayase! Um, well… I'm… really thirsty, so can I have some water?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>Can I take this barley tea?</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko </speaker>
               <p>Sure thing.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="tv">
               <speaker> Tv </speaker>
               <p>We have some shocking news that just came in! It came out into the open that
                  popular idol Shoma had a secret child! And his age wasn't 20, but actually 27!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>They need to correct his favorite food from ramen to curry, too!</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="tv">
               <speaker>Tv </speaker>
               <p>Furthermore… …he and his partner… …have not… …formally submitted… …a marriage
                  license.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko </speaker>
               <p>I could care less about that news.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken </speaker>
               <p> Miss Ayase!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p> Crap! Okarun wants to go to the bathroom!</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> Just go.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>No, but this is seriously bad news! If something blocks my view and I can't see
                  Okarun, my spell on him breaks! In other words, I have to watch Okarun as he
                  relieves himself!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> Then watch him.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>I'd never want to watch!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken</speaker>
               <p>Who would show you, anyway? That tramples upon someone else's dignity! Hey! Don't
                  look away!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo </speaker>
               <p>Don't you have any good ideas?</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>Dunno. How the hell are you holding the curse back to begin with, anyway?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p> Let's see… How do I put it… It's like I can see an aura around Okarun.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>An aura?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo </speaker>
               <p>And when I crush that aura with my hands, the aura shrinks. And the curse
                  subsides, I guess? Everyone has some kind of aura, and they come in all sorts of
                  colors. I see them on the trees and rocks there too. I can grab all those auras
                  and move them at my will, though only in a small area.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>I see. I thought psychic powers were a lot more omnipotent. Sounds like they're
                  quite limited.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>It was a lot more amazing the moment the powers awoke inside of me. That was when
                  everything I imagined turned into reality, like I was invincible!But that went
                  away real quick. I can only grab auras and stuff now.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>Momo, close your eyes for a bit.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p> No way. If I do that, my spell will be lifted.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>Basically, the problem is the reliance on your vision. Try using all of your
                  senses, such as touch. The fact that you can grab the aura means that it's
                  tactile. So close those eyes and try feeling the aura with your skin. Slowly, feel
                  it around you.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p> So cold. How am I doing?</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> Yeah. He's transformed. No good.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> Well, crap.</p>
            </sp>
         </div>
         <div type="event" xml:id="s1e3-event7">
            <stage type="location" where="ayaseHome"/>
            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker> Ken </speaker>
               <p>That really pushed me close to the limit! I won't last much longer!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>What are you gonna do, Momo? He's gonna poop any moment.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p> You're the one who told me to try that!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken</speaker>
               <p> I don't want to be watched as I relieve myself! But I wanna pee in my pants even
                  less!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>Hold on!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken </speaker>
               <p> I'm gonna borrow your bathro--</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>You've got some nerve to take a dump in someone else's house, punk!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken</speaker>
               <p>I'm pretty desperate too, you know!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker> Momo</speaker>
               <p>Why you little… Who said they'd lend you the bathroom?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken</speaker>
               <p>Are you an absolute idiot? I can piss right here if you want!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>Let me in on this too!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo </speaker>
               <p>Don't think you can run faster than me in this house!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker> Ken </speaker>
               <p>Outta my way! Or you'll have a disaster!</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>Not bad, Ken Takakura!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken </speaker>
               <p>This one is mine!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>Not letting you!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker> Ken</speaker>
               <p>This is humiliating.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>Says you.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken</speaker>
               <p>I had looked forward to experiences unknown until now, like getting abducted by
                  aliens.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo </speaker>
               <p>Seriously?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken</speaker>
               <p>But this is just too much. I want to hurry up and be released from this curse.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> Momo, you said that you were invincible when your powers first awoke.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p> Yeah.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker> Seiko </speaker>
               <p>That's likely your original power. And it seems for some reason, that power has
                  been sealed off.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>What's with that? It sounds kinda cool.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>It's a pain in the butt. You have to unleash it bit by bit through training, and
                  we don't know how long that will take. Though it's okay because it looks like that
                  boy's physical makeover will take some time.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken</speaker>
               <p>I have to be watched while going to the bathroom for a while?</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo </speaker>
               <p>That's my line…</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>Grandma, it's here! Turbo Granny! Grandma? Grandma?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>Damn you! What the hell are you doing to Grandma?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="turboGranny">
               <speaker>turboGranny</speaker>
               <p> I'm letting her choose her cause of death. A heart attack or a stroke. My curse
                  is contagious through this brat. Any human this brat sees, I can curse to death.
                  Don't underestimate me. I'm not gonna give you any time. Come to the tunnel
                  tonight. Otherwise, I'll use this brat to curse everyone around there to death.
                  That's tonight. Got that?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken</speaker>
               <p>A nosebleed…</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo </speaker>
               <p> Grandma!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> What's this?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo </speaker>
               <p> You're bleeding from your ears, too! Does your head hurt or something?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> Momo. Let's hear about what just happened.</p>
            </sp>
         </div>

         <div type="event" xml:id="s1e3-event8">
            <stage type="location" where="road"/>
            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo </speaker>
               <p>Am I seriously wearing this?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="ken">
               <speaker>Ken</speaker>
               <p>It's hard to see in front of me.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> That's a bulletproof vest against evil spirits. Make sure to keep them on. If you
                  let your guard down, you'll die quite easily.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>I know that! Despite how we look, we did defeat aliens!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>There's no such thing as aliens. Quit horsing around.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>Oh, okay.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>You bring all the trouble home in the first place because you're like that. You've
                  never listened to me ever since you were a little kid.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p> Man, so annoying! Grandma's nagging is annoying. Let's go, Okarun.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p>Momo!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p> What now? You're so naggy.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> Don't die.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>Yeah.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Seiko">
               <speaker>Seiko</speaker>
               <p> I beg of you. Please, protect those two.</p>
            </sp>
         </div>
         <div type="event" xml:id="s1e3-event9">
            <stage type="location" where="train"/>
            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker> Ken </speaker>
               <p>Why are we going by train?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>It's too far by bicycle! And you don't want to use up your stamina before we get
                  there! You seriously aren't getting off the hook, Turbo Granny!</p>
            </sp>
            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken</speaker>
               <p>I'm sorry, this is all for…</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker> Momo</speaker>
               <p>No way! That hag tried to hurts omething dear to me! I'm gonna beat Turbo Granny
                  into a pulp!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken</speaker>
               <p> Hold on, Miss Ayase You shouldn't do that here!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo </speaker>
               <p>I want to hurry up and take these off.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken</speaker>
               <p> Is it okay to do that? It's a battle uniform to protect yourself from evil
                  spirits, right? Your grandmother said keep it on.</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p>Who the hell would wear something like that? Fashion is the battle uniform for
                  gyarus! I can't get hyped up unless I wear the clothes I want to wear!</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken</speaker>
               <p>Why are you smiling?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Momo">
               <speaker>Momo</speaker>
               <p> Isn't this kinda fun?</p>
            </sp>

            <sp who="Ken">
               <speaker>Ken</speaker>
               <p>Not at all. I feel like I'm about to puke.</p>
            </sp>
         </div>



      </body>
   </text>
</TEI>
